http://www.barwrite.com/privacy.html

Privacy
Policy
BarWrite.com respects your privacy and recognizes your right to to privacy for all personal information you share with us. This includes your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, etc.
You are welcome to visit BarWrite.com anonymously. We do not collect personal information. The systems log your Internet address (IP address: the address of your computer). That is to help us learn which parts of the web site you visit. It will also show how long you spend on the individual pages. BarWrite.com does not link your IP address to any personally identifiable information. Your browser automatically informs us of its name and version number. Thus, again, BarWrite gathers no personal information.
Limited Information Gathering
Like most commercial websites, BarWrite.com uses cookies so we can better serve you when you return. Cookies are small text identifiers sent to your computer to facilitate subsequent visits. Most browsers let you define preferences so you can learn when you are sent cookies. They let you decide whether to accept or reject them. Almost all browsers let you remove cookies from your computer. Cookies cannot take information from your computer, spread viruses, or capture your e-mail address. BarWrite.com uses the information the cookies collect to track site use and improve our service to you and other visitors. BarWrite.com does not use cookies to gather personal information about you.
Choice
BarWrite.com may collect personal information that you voluntarily supply when you order products, enter contests, complete surveys, and the like. BarWrite.com clearly informs you in advance. BarWrite also explains how BarWrite will use this personal information. You have a right not to provide this information. If you choose not to provide such information, you are still welcome to visit BarWrite.com. But you may be unable to participate in certain options, offers and services.
Uses of Personal Information
If you supply BarWrite.com your postal address, you may receive periodic mailings to inform you of new products, services, events, etc. On the other hand, if you prefer NOT to receive such mailings, please let us know by contacting us.
Security
To begin with, BarWrite.com takes all appropriate and reasonable steps to protect all information you share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure. Thus, your information remains confidential to BarWrite and its assigns. We do NOT trade or rent our list. This site contains links to other sites. BarWrite.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.
Click here for our terms of use policy.
